Guide to the UE Publications Collection, 1936-1990s UE.8.1
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- The 52nd International Convention Policy, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 662)
- UE Constitution and By-laws, December 1, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 662)
- The 53rd International Convention Proceedings, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 663)
- The 53rd International Convention Policy, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 663)
- Worker Unity: Organizing and Representing Undocumented Workers, November 1987 (Box 10, Folder 663)
- UE Constitution and By-laws, December 1, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 663)
- Constitucion y Estatutos de UE, December 1, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 663)
- UE Constitution and By-laws, December 1, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 664)
- UE Shop Steward Guide, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 664)
- Ya es Hora de Mejores Sueldos (Box 10, Folder 664)
- UE-GE Appliance Service Locals Meet, April 3, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 664)
- UE Locals Deliver a Message, May-June 1989 (Box 10, Folder 664)
- Why We're Marching on April 9, March-April 1989 (Box 10, Folder 664)
- We're Back!!, January-February 1989 (Box 10, Folder 664)
- Preparing for and Conucting a Strike, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 664)
- The 54th International Convention Officers Report, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 665)
- The 54th International Convention, Convention Call, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 665)
- The 54th International Convention Draft Resolutions, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 665)
- The 54th International Convention Policy, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 665)
- Desarrollando el Activismo y la Participacion en las Uniones Locales de UE, Enero 1990 (Box 10, Folder 665)
- Building Activism and Involvement in UE Local Unions, January 1990 (Box 10, Folder 665)
- Plastics Workers Are Taking Union, January-February 1990 (Box 10, Folder 665)
- Corporate America's Biggest Export: Our Jobs (Box 10, Folder 665)
- Union Vigilance is the Best Protection, March 31, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 665)
- The 55th International Convention Officers' Report, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 666)
- The 55th International Convention Draft Resolutions, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 666)
- The 55th International Proceedings, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 666)
- The 55th International Convention Policy, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 666)
- The 55th International Convention, Convention Call, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 666)
- The 57th International Convention Proceedings, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 667)
- The 57th International Convention Policy, 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 667)
- UE Bushwacking Kit, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 667)
- Resources: Books, Packages, Pamphlets, Buttons, Pins, Stickers, Films, Videos, Slide Shows, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 667)
- Congressional Home Visit Kit, January 1992 (Box 10, Folder 667)
- The 1991 Congress UE Legislative Program and Fact Sheets (Box 10, Folder 667)
- History Screens Photographs, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 668)
- UE Constitution and By-laws, December 1, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 668)
- The 56th International Convention Officers' Report, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 668)
- The 56th International Convention Policy, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 668)
- The 58th National Convention Officers' Report, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 669)
- The 58th National Convention Proceedings, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 669)
- The 58th National Convention Policy, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 669)
- UE Constitution and By-laws, December 1, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 669)
- Plastics Workers Agree, "It Pays to Join UE", 1993 (Box 11, Folder 669)
- Trabajadores de Plasticos Dicen: "Vale la Pena Unirse a la UE", 1993 (Box 11, Folder 669)
- New Members Say, "It Pays to Join UE!!", 1993 (Box 11, Folder 669)
- UE - The Union That Makes a Difference, February 1993 (Box 11, Folder 669)
- Independent Rank and File Unionism, February 1993 (Box 11, Folder 669)
- The 59th National Convention Proceedings, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 670)
- Open Books, Tight Fists: Financial Integrity in a Rank and File Union, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 670)
- Drawing on Worker Culture, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 670)
- Them and Us: Struggles of a Rank-and-file Union, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 671)
- Fast Facts (Box 11, Folder 671)
- UE Rank-and-file Volunteers, September 1994-August 1995 (Box 11, Folder 671)
- Best of UE Steward: First Line of Defense, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 671)
- Welcome to UE, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 671)
- Welcome to UE, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 671)
- Pensions: What You Should Know, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 671)
- Local Voce: Tips On Putting Out A Local Newsletter, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 671)
- The 60th National Convention Policy, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 672)
- UE Presents: Union Predicts Company Tricks, April 1995 (Box 11, Folder 672)
- UE Presenta: El Sindicato Sabe los Trucos de las Empresas, Septiembre 1995 (Box 11, Folder 672)
- GE Service Workers Agree, "It Pays to Join UE" (Box 11, Folder 672)
- Trabajadores de Plasticos Dicen: "Vale la pena unirse a la UE" (Box 11, Folder 672)
- The Welfare Takesaway: Tearing Away the Safety Net, April 1995 (Box 11, Folder 672)
- UE Steward Pocket Guide, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 672)
- UE Steward Handbook, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 672)
- The Myth About the Money the Many Are Supposed to Have... (Box 11, Folder 673)
- The Local Publicity Committee (Box 11, Folder 674)
- ABC's of UE Complete New Members' Kit, August 1980 (Box 11, Folder 675)
- Union Scorns Plea to Settle Cone Dispute (Box 11, Folder 675)
- IUE Financial Corruption: Official Documents, February 1968 (Box 11, Folder 675)
- Men's Business Too First Edition, January 1952 (Box 11, Folder 676)
- Men's Business Too Second Edition, February 1952 (Box 11, Folder 676)
- Time to Come Back!, August 1966 (Box 11, Folder 676)
- Organized Labor and the Black Worker, October 1967 (Box 11, Folder 676)
- Guide to Political Action, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 676)
- UE Translates Words into Action!, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 676)
- Speed-up! First Edition, January 1952 (Box 11, Folder 677)
- Speed-up! Second Edition, February 1952 (Box 11, Folder 677)
- Tax Day Worrying is Not Enough...First Edition, January 1952 (Box 11, Folder 677)
- Tax Day Worrying is Not Enough...Second Edition, February 1952 (Box 11, Folder 677)
- Guess How Much Are Profits Up Since 1939? First Edition, January 1952 (Box 11, Folder 677)
- Guess How Much Profits Are U Since 1939...Second Edition, March 1952 (Box 11, Folder 677)
- The Old Shell Game First Edition, January 1952 (Box 11, Folder 677)
- The Old Shell Game Second Edition, March 1952 (Box 11, Folder 677)
- UE Steward Guide Sixth Edition, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 677)
- Watch Out for the Big Lie! Second Edition, June 23, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 677)
- Chug-chug Sixth Edition, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 677)
- UE Fights for Women Workers First Edition, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 677)
- Don't Buy Westinghouse Lamp Bulbs! (Never Circulated), April 1952 (Box 11, Folder 677)
- Watch Out for the Big Lie! First Edition, May 27, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 677)
- They All Want Them - But Cheap!, April 1952 (Box 11, Folder 677)
- UE Workers Say - Taxes Take Bigger Bites!, May 1952 (Box 11, Folder 677)
- This is the Record GE Knows It Do You?, May 1952 (Box 11, Folder 677)
- Liberty in Trouble, May 1952 (Box 11, Folder 677)
- The Emspak Case A Defense of the First Amendment and American Rights to Freedom (Box 11, Folder 677)
- The Roosevelt Spirit, May 1953 (Box 11, Folder 677)
- UE Catalogue of Publications and Publicity Services, September 1953 (Box 11, Folder 677)
- Telling the Town Through TV (Box 11, Folder 677)
- Farmer - Labor Teamwork (Box 11, Folder 677)
- IUE Founder Blasts IUE Dictatorship, April 1952 (Box 11, Folder 677)
- Peace...the Road to Full Employment, March 1952 (Box 11, Folder 677)
- Pity the Poor Boss, March 1952 (Box 11, Folder 677)
- One Day Out of Four You Work for the Tax Collectors..., March 1952 (Box 11, Folder 677)
- Unfair! Yes, and Very Expensive..., March 1952 (Box 11, Folder 677)
- The Shameful Record of IUE-CIO Leaders in the Otis Strike..., February 1952 (Box 11, Folder 677)
- Union Busting in Brockport - How GE Won, October 1968 (Box 11, Folder 677)
- Newspapers Recieved by UE News Department (Box 11, Folder 678)
- Movie Script, May 31, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 678)
- UE Catalogue of Publications and Publicity Services, September 1953 (Box 11, Folder 679)
- Dare to be Free (Box 11, Folder 679)
- Basic Statement of United Electrical, Radion and Machine Workers of America, October 1953 (Box 11, Folder 679)
- The Role of Labor Today, September 10, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 679)
- The Concept of Labor Unity in the 1970's, November 1974 (Box 11, Folder 679)
- While UE Battles (Box 11, Folder 679)
- A Message from UE-CIO to Every General Electric, Westinghouse and General Motors Employee (Box 11, Folder 679)
- Ask 'Red Infiltration' Charge Dismissal - US Drops Fight with UE, March 24, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 679)
- UE Challenges Westinghouse to Halt Discrimination Against Married Women, March 11, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 679)
- IUE Blasts IBEW - IBEW Blasts IUE, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 679)
- Depression! Must We Suffer Another 1929? (Box 11, Folder 679)
- Has Anyone Bothered to Ask You How You're Doing Since the 1966 GE Settlement was Made?, December 1966 (Box 11, Folder 679)
- Industry's Weapon...Company Unionism!, January 1950 (Box 11, Folder 679)
- The Un-American Activities Committee is the Most Un-American Thing in America, April 8, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 679)
- Time is Running Out (Box 11, Folder 679)
- Ethics as Practiced by IAM, February 1959 (Box 11, Folder 679)
- They Want to Turn the Clock Back (Box 11, Folder 679)
- Organization Draft (Box 11, Folder 679)
- The UE Steward Facts and Figures for Union Leaders, March 1948 (Box 11, Folder 680)
- The UE Steward Facts and Figures for Union Leaders, April, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 680)
- The UE Steward Facts and Figures for Union Leaders, November 1948 (Box 11, Folder 680)
- UE Steward - Jobs - A Letter to the President, April 1949 (Box 11, Folder 681)
- UE Steward Settling that Grievance, May 1949 (Box 11, Folder 681)
- UE Steward Women Fight for Higher Wages, June 1949 (Box 11, Folder 681)
- UE Steward UE - Vacation Pioneer, July 1949 (Box 11, Folder 681)
- UE Steward UE Goes to Convention, August 1949 (Box 11, Folder 681)
- UE Steward Challenges to UE Members, September 1949 (Box 11, Folder 681)
- UE Steward Special Convention Issue, October 1949 (Box 11, Folder 681)
- UE Steward "We Must Think Things Out", November-December 1949 (Box 11, Folder 681)
- UE Steward In Unity There is Strength, January-February 1950 (Box 11, Folder 682)
- UE Steward Christmas is Coming, December 1951 (Box 11, Folder 682)
- UE Steward Up, Up - But Why?, January 1952 (Box 11, Folder 683)
- UE Steward Chowderhead Rides Again, February 1952 (Box 11, Folder 683)
- UE Steward What Price Double Standard, March 1952 (Box 11, Folder 683)
- UE Steward What Price Discrimination?, April 1952 (Box 11, Folder 683)
- UE Steward Liberty in Trouble!, May 1952 (Box 11, Folder 683)
- UE Steward Smith Bill - Danger!, June 1952 (Box 11, Folder 683)
- UE Steward Vacations Were Won!, July 1952 (Box 11, Folder 683)
- UE Steward Olympics, August 1952 (Box 11, Folder 683)
- UE Steward UE 17th Convention Issue, September 1952 (Box 11, Folder 683)
- UE Steward "We're Building the Union!" Say Delegates at 17th UE Convention, October 1952 (Box 11, Folder 683)
- UE Steward What Do You Do When Your Job Disappears?, November 1952 (Box 11, Folder 683)
- UE Steward Christmas Time is Peace Time, December 1952 (Box 11, Folder 683)
- UE Steward The Grand Jury Breaks the Law, January 1953 (Box 11, Folder 684)
- UE Steward T-H Board Attack Illegal, February 1953 (Box 11, Folder 684)
- UE Steward Faster Time is Visiting Time, March 1953 (Box 11, Folder 684)
- UE Steward F.D.R. Anniversary Issue, April 1953 (Box 11, Folder 684)
- UE Steward UE Victory at Tug-Sol!, June 1953 (Box 11, Folder 684)
- UE Steward The Big Steal, July 1953 (Box 11, Folder 684)
- UE Steward Summer Time si Play Time!, August 1953 (Box 11, Folder 684)
- UE Steward Special Issue: What is McCarthyism?, September 1953 (Box 11, Folder 684)
- UE Steward Convention Issue, October 1953 (Box 11, Folder 684)
- UE Steward Two UE Stewards Answer Sen. Butler, November-December 1953 (Box 11, Folder 684)
- UE Steward How Secure is Social Security?, January 1954 (Box 11, Folder 685)
- UE Steward Stop the Butler Bill!, February 1954 (Box 11, Folder 685)
- UE Steward It Pays to Belong to UE, March 1954 (Box 11, Folder 685)
- UE Steward Their Future: The Roosevelt Way? The McCarthy Way?, April-May 1954 (Box 11, Folder 685)
- UE Steward, June 1954 (Box 11, Folder 685)
- UE Steward Report on UE's Fighting 19h National Convention, October-November 1954 (Box 11, Folder 685)
- UE Steward Special Issue: The Shorter Work-Week, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 686)
- Strikes...and the Communists Behind Them, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 687)
- UE The Members Run This Union! with You Are in Danger! and Monopoly, March 1947 (Box 12, Folder 688)
- Membership Book, April 1963 (Box 12, Folder 689)
- Report on IUE Convention, September 1964 (Box 12, Folder 690)
- Strike Benefits, September 1968 (Box 12, Folder 691)
- All of Us Built America, October 1968 (Box 12, Folder 692)
- The Young Worker Challenges the Union Establishment, July 1969 (Box 12, Folder 693)
- UE Policy on Strike Assistance, November 1969 (Box 12, Folder 694)
- Labor Unity, December 1970 (Box 12, Folder 695)
- He Fought for His Union, January 1972 (Box 12, Folder 696)
- Safeguarding the Union's Integrity, January 1974 (Box 12, Folder 697)
- Bori H. Block to General Vice Presidents, International Representatives and Field Organizers, January 16, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 698)
- The Fight to Save Jobs and Stop Plant Closings, February 1983 (Box 12, Folder 699)
- Automation and Job - Who Decides?, March 1984 (Box 12, Folder 700)
- A Plea for Sanity: Must We Perish?, September 1984 (Box 12, Folder 701)
- Here is the Proof! (Box 12, Folder 702)
- Department of Justice Admits Red Smear Against UE A Fraud (Box 12, Folder 703)
- UE Foundry Safety and Health Manual (Box 12, Folder 704)
- UE Lead the Fight Against Litton's Union Busting (Box 12, Folder 705)
- The 1st UE Annual Convention General Officers Reports, September 1936 (Box 12, Folder 706)
- The 2nd UE Annual Convention General Officers Report, September 1937 (Box 12, Folder 707)
- The 2nd UE Annual Convention General Officers Report, September 1937 (Box 12, Folder 708)
- The 9th UE International Convention General Officers Report, September 1943 (Box 12, Folder 709)
- The 11th UE International Convention General Officers Report, September 1946 (Box 12, Folder 710)
- The 12th UE International Convention General Officers Report, September 1947 (Box 12, Folder 711)
- The 13th UE International Convention General Officers Report, September 1948 (Box 12, Folder 712)
- The 14th UE International Convention General Officers Report, September 1949 (Box 12, Folder 713)
- The 15th UE International Convention General Officers Report, September 1950 (Box 12, Folder 714)
- The 16th UE International Convention General Officers Report, September 1951 (Box 12, Folder 715)
- The 17th UE International Convention General Officers Report, September 1952 (Box 12, Folder 716)
- The 18th UE International Convention General Officers Report, September 1953 (Box 12, Folder 717)
- The 19th UE International Convention General Officers Report, September 1954 (Box 12, Folder 718)
- The 20th UE International Convention General Officers Report, September 1955 (Box 12, Folder 719)
- The 21st UE International Convention General Officers Report, September 1956 (Box 12, Folder 720)
- The 22nd UE International Convention General Officers Report, August 1957 (Box 12, Folder 721)
- The 23rd UE International Convention General Officers Report, September 1958 (Box 12, Folder 722)
- The 24th UE International Convention General Officers Report, September 1959 (Box 12, Folder 723)
- The 25th UE International Convention General Officers Report, September 1960 (Box 12, Folder 724)
- The 26th UE International Convention General Officers Report, September 1961 (Box 12, Folder 725)
- The 27th UE International Convention General Officers Report, August 1962 (Box 12, Folder 726)
- The 28th UE International Convention General Officers Report, September 1963 (Box 12, Folder 727)
- The 29th UE International Convention General Officers Report, September 1964 (Box 12, Folder 728)
- The 30th UE International Convention General Officers Report, September 1965 (Box 12, Folder 729)
- The 31st UE International Convention General Officers Report, June 1966 (Box 12, Folder 730)
- The 32nd UE International Convention General Officers Report, August 1967 (Box 12, Folder 731)
- The 33rd UE International Convention General Officers Report, September 1968 (Box 12, Folder 732)
- The 34th UE International Convention General Officers Report, September 1969 (Box 12, Folder 733)
- The 37th UE International Convention General Officers Report, September 1972 (Box 12, Folder 734)
- The 38th UE International Convention General Officers Report, September 1973 (Box 12, Folder 735)
- The 39th UE International Convention General Officers Report, September 1974 (Box 12, Folder 736)
- The 40th UE International Convention General Officers Report, September 1975 (Box 12, Folder 737)
- The 41st UE International Convention General Officers Report, September 1976 (Box 12, Folder 738)
- The 42nd UE International Convention General Officers Report, September 1977 (Box 12, Folder 739)
- The 43rd UE International Convention General Officers Report, September 1978 (Box 12, Folder 740)
- Proposed Amendments to the Constitution, September 1939 (Box 12, Folder 741)
- Proposed Resolutions to the Convention, September 1939 (Box 12, Folder 741)
- Proposed Amendments to the Constitution, September 1940 (Box 13, Folder 742)
- Proposed Resolutions to the Convention, September 1940 (Box 13, Folder 742)
- Proposed Resolutions and Amendments to the Convention, September 1941 (Box 13, Folder 743)
- Proposed Resolutions and Amendments to the Convention, September 1943 (Box 13, Folder 744)
- Proposed Resolutions and Constitutional Amendments for the 10th International Convention, September 1944 (Box 13, Folder 745)
- Proposed Resolutions and Constitutional Amendments for the 13th International Convention, September 1948 (Box 13, Folder 746)
- Proposed Resolutions and Constitutional Amendments for the 15th International Convention, September 1950 (Box 13, Folder 747)
- Proposed Resolutions and Constitutional Amendments for the 16th International Convention, September 1951 (Box 13, Folder 748)
- Proposed Resolutions and Constitutional Amendments for the 17th International Convention, September 1952 (Box 13, Folder 749)
- Proposed Resolutions and Constitutional Amendments for the 18th Annual Convention, September 1953 (Box 13, Folder 780)
- Proposed Resolutions and Constitutional Amendments for the 19th International Convention, September 1954 (Box 13, Folder 781)
- Proposed Resolutions and Constitutional Amendments for the 20th International Convention, September 1955 (Box 13, Folder 782)
- Proposed Resolutions and Constitutional Amendments for the 21st International Convention, September 1956 (Box 13, Folder 783)
- Proposed Resolutions and Constitutional Amendments for the 22nd International Convention, August 1957 (Box 13, Folder 784)
- Proposed Resolutions and Constitutional Amendments for the 23rd International Convention, September 1958 (Box 13, Folder 785)
- Proposed Resolutions and Constitutional Amendments for the 24th International Convention, September 1959 (Box 13, Folder 786)
- Proposed Resolutions and Constitutional Amendments for the 25th International Convention, September 1960 (Box 13, Folder 787)
- Proposed Resolutions and Amendments for the 26th International Convention, September 1961 (Box 13, Folder 788)
- Proposed Resolutions and Amendments for the 27th International Convention, August 1962 (Box 13, Folder 789)
- The 8th UE International Convention Resolutions, September 1942 (Box 13, Folder 790)
- The 9th International Convention Policy, September 1943 (Box 13, Folder 791)
- The 10th International Convention Policy, September 1944 (Box 13, Folder 792)
- The 11th International Convention Policy, September 1946 (Box 13, Folder 793)
- The 12th International Convention Policy, September 1947 (Box 13, Folder 794)
- The 13th International Convention Policy, September 1948 (Box 13, Folder 795)
- The 15th International Convention Policy, September 1950 (Box 13, Folder 796)
- The 16th International Convention Policy, September 1951 (Box 13, Folder 797)
- The 17th International Convention Policy, September 1952 (Box 13, Folder 798)
- The 18th International Convention Policy, September 1953 (Box 13, Folder 799)
- The 19th International Convention Policy, September 1954 (Box 13, Folder 800)
- The 20th International Convention Policy, September 1955 (Box 13, Folder 801)
- The 21st International Convention Policy, September 1956 (Box 13, Folder 802)
- The 22nd International Convention Policy, August 1957 (Box 13, Folder 803)
- The 23rd International Convention Policy, September 1958 (Box 13, Folder 804)
- The 24th International Convention Policy, September 1959 (Box 13, Folder 805)
- The 25th International Convention Policy, September 1960 (Box 13, Folder 806)
- The 26th International Convention Policy, September 1961 (Box 13, Folder 807)
- The 27th International Convention Policy, August 1962 (Box 13, Folder 808)
- The 28th International Convention Policy, September 1963 (Box 13, Folder 809)
- The 29th International Convention Policy, September 1964 (Box 13, Folder 810)
- The 30th International Convention Policy, September 1965 (Box 13, Folder 811)
- The 31st International Convention Policy, June 1966 (Box 13, Folder 812)
- The 32st International Convention Policy, August 1967 (Box 13, Folder 813)
- The 33rd International Convention Policy, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 814)
- The 34th International Convention Policy, September 1969 (Box 13, Folder 815)
- The 37th International Convention Policy, September 1972 (Box 13, Folder 816)
- The 38th International Convention Policy, September 1973 (Box 13, Folder 817)
- The 39th International Convention Policy, September 1974 (Box 13, Folder 818)
- The 40th International Convention Policy, September 1975 (Box 13, Folder 819)
- The 41st International Convention Policy, September 1976 (Box 13, Folder 820)
- The 42nd International Convention Policy, September 1977 (Box 13, Folder 821)
- The 43rd International Convention Policy, September 1978 (Box 13, Folder 822)
- The 45th International Convention General Officers Report, September 1980 (Box 13, Folder 823, Box 14)
- The 47th International Convention General Officers Report, September 1982 (Box 14, Folder 824)
- The 48th International Convention General Officers Report, September 1983 (Box 14, Folder 825)
- The 51st International Convention General Officers Report, September 1986 (Box 14, Folder 826)
- The 45th International Convention Policy, September 1980 (Box 14, Folder 827)
- The 46th International Convention Policy, September 1981 (Box 14, Folder 828)
- The 47th International Convention Policy, September 1982 (Box 14, Folder 829)
- The 48th International Convention Policy, September 1983 (Box 14, Folder 830)
- The 49th International Convention Policy, September 1984 (Box 14, Folder 831)
- The 50th International Convention Policy, September 1985 (Box 14, Folder 832)
- The 51st International Convention Policy, September 1986 (Box 14, Folder 833)
- The 53rd International Convention Policy, August 1988 (Box 14, Folder 834)
- The 1st International Convention Proceedings, March 1936 (Box 14, Folder 835)
- The 1st Annual Convention Proceedings, September 1936 (Box 14, Folder 836)
- The 1st Annual Convention Proceedings, September 1936 (Box 14, Folder 837)
- The 3rd Annual Convention Proceedings, September 1938 (Box 14, Volume 1)
- The 6th National Convention Proceedings, September 1940 (Box 14, Volume 2)
- The 7th International Convention Proceedings, September 1941 (Box 14, Volume 3)